Department of Drama and Dance Records UA070
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Drama Department photographic slides of productions, 1959 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2000; UA070.003; 3.0 Linear Feet; 46 Digital Object(s)
  - Androcles and the Lion, 1983; UA070.003.045.00019 (Box 45)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 64B; Original description: Major
  - Androcles and the Lion, 1983; UA070.003.045.00020 (Box 45)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original box #: Box 64A; Original description: Major
  - Exit the King, 1983; UA070.003.046.00001 (Box 46)
    Director: Barbara Schofield. Original box #: Box 65A; Original description: Masters
  - Exit the King, 1983; UA070.003.046.00002 (Box 46)
    Director: Barbara Schofield. Original box #: Box 65B; Original description: Masters
    - Scene from Exit the King, 1983-11-01; UA070.003.046.00002.00001 (Box 46)
      Theater; Drama; Plays; Students; Theater; photographic print; Ionesco, Eugène
  - Restoration, 1983; UA070.003.046.00003 (Box 46)
    Director: Kalman Burnim. Original box #: Box 66B; Original description: Major
  - Restoration, 1983; UA070.003.046.00004 (Box 46)
    Director: Kalman Burnim. Original box #: Box 66A; Original description: Major
  - Suddenly Last Summer, 1984; UA070.003.046.00005 (Box 46)
    Original description: 3 P's
  - VAT2LAV, 1984; UA070.003.046.00006 (Box 46)
    Director: Vincent Murphy. Original Box #: Box 67A and B; Original description: Major
    - Scene from VAT2LAV, 1984-03-01; UA070.003.046.00006.00016 (Box 46)
      Theater; Drama; Plays; Students; Costumes; photographic print
  - The Lower Depths, 1984; UA070.003.046.00007 (Box 46)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original Box #: Box 68B; Original description: Major
    - Six students in a scene from The Lower Depths, 1984-05-01; UA070.003.046.00007.00009 (Box 46)
      Director: Downing Cless. Five male students look at a sixth male student in a dance pose in a scene from a university production of The Lower Depths.
      Plays; Actors; Students; slide (photograph); Gorky, Maxim; Department of Drama and Dance
  - The Lower Depths, 1984; UA070.003.046.00008 (Box 46)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original Box #: Box 68A
  - The Year Boston Won the Pennant, 1984; UA070.003.046.00009 (Box 46)
    Director: Downing Cless
  - Uncle Vanya, 1984; UA070.003.046.00010 (Box 46)
    Director: Vincent Murphy. Original box #: Box B; Original description: Major
    - Scene from Uncle Vanya, 1984-12-01; UA070.003.046.00010.00001 (Box 46)
      Theater; Plays; Drama; Students; photographic print; Chekhov, Anton Pavlovich, 1860-1904
  - Uncle Vanya, 1984; UA070.003.046.00011 (Box 46)
    Director: Vincent Murphy. Original box #: Box A; Original description: Major
  - No Exit, 1985; UA070.003.046.00012 (Box 46)
    Director: Peter Arnott
  - Pathways to Madness, 1985; UA070.003.046.00013 (Box 46)
    Director: Vincent Murphy. Original Description: Major
  - The Belle of Amherst, 1985; UA070.003.046.00014 (Box 46)
  - The Deadly Game, 1985; UA070.003.046.00015 (Box 46)
    Original box #: Box B
  - The Deadly Game, 1985; UA070.003.046.00016 (Box 46)
    Original box #: Box A
  - Bedroom Farce, 1985; UA070.003.046.00017 (Box 46)
  - Bedroom Farce, 1985; UA070.003.046.00018 (Box 46)
    Original box #: Box C
  - Bedroom Farce, 1985; UA070.003.046.00019 (Box 46)
  - Easy Targets by Marc Diamond, 1985; UA070.003.047.00001 (Box 47)
    No Sound
  - The Matchmaker, 1985; UA070.003.047.00002 (Box 47)
    Original Box #: Box B
  - The Matchmaker, 1985; UA070.003.047.00003 (Box 47)
    Original Box #: Box A
  - A Doll's House, 1986; UA070.003.047.00004 (Box 47)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 2
  - A Doll's House, 1986; UA070.003.047.00005 (Box 47)
    Director: Peter Arnott. Original box #: Box 1
  - Love and Intrigue, 1986; UA070.003.047.00006 (Box 47)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 2; Original description: Major
  - Love and Intrigue, 1986; UA070.003.047.00007 (Box 47)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original box #: Box 1; Original description: Major
  - Beyond Therapy, 1986; UA070.003.047.00008 (Box 47)
  - JB / Beyond Therapy, 1986; UA070.003.047.00009 (Box 47)
  - J.B., 1986; UA070.003.047.00010 (Box 47)
  - Arms and the Man, 1986; UA070.003.047.00011 (Box 47)
  - Arms and the Man, 1986; UA070.003.047.00012 (Box 47)
  - Lysis Trata, 1986; UA070.003.047.00013 (Box 47)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box B; Original description: Major
  - Lysis Trata, 1986; UA070.003.047.00014 (Box 47)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original box #: Box A; Original description: Major
  - In the 4th Decade And..., 1986; UA070.003.047.00015 (Box 47)
    Director: Lisa Hillyer. Original box #: Box C; Original description: Major
  - In the 4th Decade And..., 1986; UA070.003.047.00016 (Box 47)
    Director: Lisa Hillyer. Original box #: Box B; Original description: Major
  - In the 4th Decade And..., 1986; UA070.003.047.00017 (Box 47)
    Director: Lisa Hillyer. Original box #: Box A; Original description: Major
  - Fanshen, 1987; UA070.003.047.00018 (Box 47)
    Director: Bruce Shapiro. Original description: Major
  - The Madman & the Nun, 1987; UA070.003.048.00001 (Box 48)
    Director: Bill Reichblum. Original description: Major
  - The Madman & the Nun, 1987; UA070.003.048.00002 (Box 48)
  - The Madman & the Nun, 1987; UA070.003.048.00003 (Box 48)
  - Private Lives, 1987; UA070.003.048.00004 (Box 48)
    Director: Roy Steinberg.
  - Fifth of July, 1987; UA070.003.048.00005 (Box 48)
    Director: Pam Bongas
  - Harvey, 1987; UA070.003.048.00006 (Box 48)
    Director: Jeffrey Martin. Original description: Summer Theater
  - Harvey, 1987; UA070.003.048.00007 (Box 48)
    Director: Jeffrey Martin. Original description: Summer
  - Two for the Seesaw, 1987; UA070.003.048.00008 (Box 48)
    Director: Bruce Shapiro
  - Love's Comedy, 1987; UA070.003.048.00009 (Box 48)
  - Anouilh's Antigone, 1988; UA070.003.048.00010 (Box 48)
  - Tartuffe by Moliere, 1988; UA070.003.048.00011 (Box 48)
    Director: Peter Davis. Original description: Major
  - Tartuffe by Moliere, 1988; UA070.003.048.00012 (Box 48)
  - Scenes from American Life, 1988; UA070.003.048.00013 (Box 48)
    Director: Vincent Murphy
  - Largo Desolato/ Catastrophe, Iconicity by Bruce Shapiro, 1989; UA070.003.048.00014 (Box 48)
  - Largo Desolato/ Catastrophe, Iconicity by Bruce Shapiro, 1989; UA070.003.048.00015 (Box 48)
  - A View from the Bridge, 1989; UA070.003.048.00016 (Box 48)
    Director Sherwood Collins
  - A View from the Bridge, 1989; UA070.003.048.00017 (Box 48)
  - A View from the Bridge, 1989; UA070.003.048.00018 (Box 48)
  - Marat / Sade, 1989; UA070.003.049.00001 (Box 49)
    - Six students in a scene from Murat/Sade, 1989-10-17; UA070.003.049.00001.00016; Unknown (Box 49)
      Director: Downing Cless. A couple holding hands, a maid sitting, and a man writing in a scene from a university production of Murat/Sade.
      Actors; Plays; Students; slide (photograph); Dept. of Drama and Dance; Weiss, Peter, 1916-1982
  - The Handmaid's Tale, novel by Margaret Atwood, adapted and iconicity by Bruce Shapiro, 1989; UA070.003.049.00002 (Box 49)
  - The Man who Hated People, 1990; UA070.003.049.00003 (Box 49)
    Director: Sherwood Collins. Original description: Major Production
  - Cloud 9, 1990; UA070.003.049.00004 (Box 49)
    Director: Marianne Kubic. Original description: Major
  - Noises Off, 1990; UA070.003.049.00005 (Box 49)
    Director: Neal Hirsig
  - The Eumenides, 1990; UA070.003.049.00006 (Box 49)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991; UA070.003.049.00007 (Box 49)
    - Four students perform in a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991-04-01; UA070.003.049.00007.00008; Unknown (Box 49)
      Director: Downing Cless. This play was performed from 1991-04-11 to 1991-04-14 and 1991-04-18 to 1991-04-20.
      People; Actors; Plays; Students; slide (photograph); Dept. of Drama and Dance
    - Acting troupe in a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991-04-01; UA070.003.049.00007.00012; Unknown (Box 49)
    - Lysander, Puck, and ten fairies in a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991-04-01; UA070.003.049.00007.00017; Unknown (Box 49)
    - Titania seduces Nick Bottom in a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991-04-01; UA070.003.049.00007.00019; Unknown (Box 49)
    - Fairies in a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991-04-01; UA070.003.049.00007.00021; Unknown (Box 49)
    - Puck and six fairies in a Midsummer Night's Dream, 1991-04-01; UA070.003.049.00007.00022; Unknown (Box 49)
  - Quietus by Cindy Cooper, 1991; UA070.003.049.00008 (Box 49)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1991; UA070.003.049.00009 (Box 49)
  - "Best of" Arena Slides, 1992 -- 1996; UA070.003.049.00010 (Box 49)
  - The Golden Age, 1992; UA070.003.049.00011 (Box 49)
  - The Birds, 1992; UA070.003.049.00012 (Box 49)
    Director: Downing Cless. Original description: 7814
    - Five students perform in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00003; Unknown (Box 49)
      Director: Downing Cless. This play was performed from 1992-04-07 through 1992-04-12.
    - Student dressed as a bird performs in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00007; Unknown (Box 49)
      People; Actors; Plays; Students; Costumes; slide (photograph); Dept. of Drama and Dance
    - Student in a bird costume performs in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00010 (Box 49)
    - Seven students perform in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00011 (Box 49)
    - Six students perform in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00016 (Box 49)
    - Three students perform in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00017 (Box 49)
    - Six students perform in the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00019 (Box 49)
    - Set design for the Birds, 1992-04-01; UA070.003.049.00012.00025 (Box 49)
  - Our Town, 1992; UA070.003.049.00013 (Box 49)
    Director: Sherwood Collins
  - The Crackwalker by Judith Thompson, 1993; UA070.003.049.00014 (Box 49)
  - The Three Penny Opera, 1993; UA070.003.049.00015 (Box 49)
  - Ghetto, 1993; UA070.003.049.00016 (Box 49)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original description: 1 / 2, 9578
  - Ghetto, 1993; UA070.003.049.00017 (Box 49)
    Director: Laurence Senelick. Original description: 2 / 2, 9578
  - Machinal, 1994; UA070.003.049.00018 (Box 49)
  - Our Country's Good, 1994; UA070.003.050.00001 (Box 50)
    Director: Barbara Grossman. Original description: 2 / 2
  - Our Country's Good, 1994; UA070.003.050.00002 (Box 50)
    Director: Barbara Grossman. Original description: 1 / 2
  - The Winter's Tale by William Shakespeare, 1994; UA070.003.050.00003 (Box 50)
    Director: Anthony Cornish
  - The Kentucky Cycle by Schenkkan, 1995; UA070.003.050.00004 (Box 50)
  - The Kentucky Cycle by Schenkkan, 1995; UA070.003.050.00005 (Box 50)
  - The Kentucky Cycle by Schenkkan, 1995; UA070.003.050.00006 (Box 50)
  - The Visit by Dverrenmatt, 1995; UA070.003.050.00007 (Box 50)
    Director: William Sun. Original box #: 2192
  - Stage Door by Ferber & Kaufman, 1995; UA070.003.050.00008 (Box 50)
  - Stage Door by Ferber & Kaufman, 1995; UA070.003.050.00009 (Box 50)
  - Stage Door by Ferber & Kaufman, 1995; UA070.003.050.00010 (Box 50)
  - Henry V, 1996; UA070.003.050.00011 (Box 50)
    Director: Robert O'Hara
  - Henry V, 1996; UA070.003.050.00012 (Box 50)
  - Henry V, 1996; UA070.003.050.00013 (Box 50)
  - Henry V, 1996; UA070.003.050.00014 (Box 50)
  - The Learned Ladies by Moliere, 1996; UA070.003.050.00015 (Box 50)
    Director: Barbara Grossman
  - The Hostage, 1996; UA070.003.050.00016 (Box 50)
    Director: Laurence Selenick
  - The Hostage, 1996; UA070.003.050.00017 (Box 50)
  - Hamlet, 1997; UA070.003.050.00018 (Box 50)
  - Hamlet, 1997; UA070.003.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - Alice in Wonderland, 1997; UA070.003.051.00002 (Box 51)
  - Alice in Wonderland, 1997; UA070.003.051.00003 (Box 51)
  - Alice in Wonderland, 1997; UA070.003.051.00004 (Box 51)
  - Peer Gynt, 1997; UA070.003.051.00005 (Box 51)
  - Peer Gynt, 1997; UA070.003.051.00006 (Box 51)
  - Peer Gynt, 1997; UA070.003.051.00007 (Box 51)
  - The Raw, the Cooked, and the Rotten, 1998; UA070.003.051.00008 (Box 51)
    Director: Judith Williams
  - The Raw, the Cooked, and the Rotten, 1998; UA070.003.051.00009 (Box 51)
  - The Illusion by Tony Kushner, 1998; UA070.003.051.00010 (Box 51)
  - The Inspector General, 1998; UA070.003.051.00011 (Box 51)
    Director: Laurence Senelick
  - The Inspector General, 1998; UA070.003.051.00012 (Box 51)
  - Macbeth, 1999; UA070.003.051.00013 (Box 51)
    Director: Anthony Cornish. Original box #: Box 1
  - Macbeth, 1999; UA070.003.051.00014 (Box 51)
    Director: Anthony Cornish. Original box #: Box 2
  - Arcadia, 1999; UA070.003.051.00015 (Box 51)
  - Love for Love, 1999; UA070.003.051.00016 (Box 51)
  - Love for Love, 1999; UA070.003.051.00017 (Box 51)
  - Skin of our Teeth, 2000; UA070.003.051.00018 (Box 51)
  - Skin of our Teeth, 2000; UA070.003.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Hayavadana, 2000; UA070.003.052.00002 (Box 52)
    Director: Sudipto Cha Herjee
  - Easy Targets, 1985-10-26; UA070.003.052.00003 (Box 52)
    By Mark Diamond. No sound.
    videocassette
  - Tartuffe by Moliere, 1988-04-18; UA070.003.052.00004 (Box 52)
    Director: P. Davis. Tufts Arena Theater.
  - In the Fourth Decade and..., 1986 -- 1987; UA070.003.052.00005 (Box 52)
    Created and directed by Lisa F. Hiller
  - In the Fourth Decade and..., 1986 -- 1987; UA070.003.052.00006 (Box 52)
    Created and directed by Lisa F. Hiller.
  - A Conversation with Stephen Sondheim, 2004-04-12; UA070.003.052.00007 (Box 52)
    DVD
- Additional accessions, 1940-2009; UA070.004
  - Drama Department - Programs, Prompt Books, 1984 -- 1985; UA070-002 (Box 1)
  - Drama Department - Programs and Scrapbooks, UA070-003 (Box 2)
  - Drama Department - Programs, Prompt Books, 1943 -- 1982; UA070-004 (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1940 -- 1959; UA070-005 (Box 4)
  - Drama Department - Files, 1947 -- 1970; UA070-006 (Box 5)
  - Drama Department - Scrapbooks, UA070-007 (Box 6)
  - Drama Department - Scrapbooks, UA070-008 (Box 7)
  - Programs and scripts and press clippings, 1947 -- 1958; UA070-009 (Box 8)
  - Oversized Fliers, 1947 -- 1958; UA070-010 (Box 9)
  - Drama Department - 3Ps, UA070-011 (Box 10)
  - Balch Arena Theater, 1996-97 Season Announcement, 1996 -- 1997; UA070-012 (Box 11)
  - Scrapbook, 1956-02-10 -- 1959; UA070-013 (Box 12)
  - Histories and Timelines, 1940 -- 1950; UA070-014 (Box 13)
  - Scripts, UA070-015 (Box 14)
  - Plans 'Ecclesiasusae', 1976; UA070-016 (Box 15)
  - Plans 'Endgame', 1976; UA070-017 (Box 16)
  - Plans 'The Crucible', 1976; UA070-018 (Box 17)
  - Plans 'Ghosts', 1976; UA070-019 (Box 18)
  - Plans 'Threepenny Opera', 1977; UA070-020 (Box 19)
  - Plans 'Media', 1976 -- 1977; UA070-021 (Box 20)
  - Drama Posters, UA070-022 (Box 21)
  - Various theater group mailings and slides, 1979 -- 2009; UA070-023 (Box 22)
    Added slides from Major Barbara (1980-03) production on 2011-04-11; Added slides from Downing Cless (2013.127) on 2013-06-26. Added Magic Circle flyers.
  - Lysistrata Poster, 2018; UA070-027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 22)
  - Theater Scrapbooks, 1960 -- 1971; UA070-024 (Box 23)
  - Arena Theater production photographs, 1964 -- 1970; UA070-025 (Box 24)
  - Arena Theater slides and video, 1976 -- 2009; UA070-026 (Box 25)